goconqr.com 2019-06-05

# GoConqr - Privacy Policy

The GoConqr Privacy Policy outlines your data privacy rights on the GoConqr platform and details our approach to managing your data. This policy (together with our  Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to within it) documents the personal data we collect from you, what we use that data for, and how you can control and access the data. 

We have made revisions to our policy, effective 25th May 2018, to reflect the best practices as outlined by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and we seek to comply fully with all the conditions therein for both members and visitors. 

This policy covers the following areas: 

  * Information we may collect from you
  * How we use the data collected
  * How to access and control your data
  * Cookies
  * Important privacy info
  * Specific services
  * Changes to privacy policy
  * Contact

##  INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU 

GoConqr captures various elements of information as you register and browse the site, this information may include: 

**Personal information for registration and use of the website:** If you register to become a member of GoConqr you will provide information that will help keep your account unique and private – this may include name, email address, age or social media login access. You may also provide additional information about your learning stage and interests. This information is used to improve your experience on GoConqr by providing you with relevant suggestions for learning material and learning groups. 

**Details of your visits to GoConqr:** We will also capture information about your visit from your browser. This may include IP address and device type. This information is used to present you with a more relevant experience based on your location and for diagnostic purposes. Information is also passed on to Google Analytics for our reporting purposes. All information passed to Google Analytics is on an anonymous basis and is non-identifiable. This is statistical data about your use of our Service, and does not identify you or any individual. 

**Cookies:** Our Service uses cookies to store information about your visit. These cookies are stored by us to support the core operation of the Service. In addition, our third-party partners may also store cookies on your browser for one or more of the following reasons: to measure site performance, to gather non-identifiable user statistics and analytics, to provide targeted advertising. See more information on the cookies we use below. 

###  Information we gather from third-parties with your consent 

As part of our functionality we offer you the opportunity to connect with your friends who already use GoConqr. When selecting this option you give us authority to: 

  1. View your Facebook Friends and your contacts on GMail, Yahoo or Microsoft email services, 
  2. Compare these against our database of GoConqr users, and 
  3. Where there is a match, to offer you the option of connecting with your friend through GoConqr. 

When you choose the option to connect, your friend will have the opportunity to either accept or decline this connection request. All connections with Facebook, Gmail, Yahoo and Microsoft are done through their standard channels. We do not store any of these contact details. 

Allowing us to do this is optional, and will only be carried out when you, the user, explicitly access this functionality. 

##  HOW WE USE THE DATA COLLECTED 

###  Providing the GoConqr service 

Details provided when you register with us allow you to manage your account and keep it private. It also allows us to personalise certain elements. 

When you sign up we also ask you for information about your learning level and subjects / interests. This allows us to make suggestions of learning material that we think may be of interest to you. Similarly we will suggest learning Groups on GoConqr that we think may be of benefit to you. 

We also will track general usage (not identifiable) and performance statistics to allow us to the make improvements and introduce new features to the platform. 

###  Communication 

We will use the email address provided to us to communicate a number of product messages regarding the platform in general and more specific notifications regarding areas of interest to you. By signing up to GoConqr you agree to allow GoConqr to send emails to the email address that you have provided for the setup of your account and to help you get started. You are also aware that, for the best new-user experience, we will initialize all your email preferences such that they are switched on. This can be easily changed by following the link in the next paragraph. 

You have full control over which emails you will receive from us. You can manage your email preferences in your   Account section. 

###  Advertising 

Almost all GoConqr members and visitors access and use the platform for free. In order to sustain this free service we use advertising to generate revenue to support the running and development of the platform. 

**Information shared on GoConqr:**

We may use data we collect through our interactions with you – for example location, learning level or learning interest – and share this anonymously with our advertising third-parties, (see list below), so that they can select and deliver some of the ads you see on our platform. Therefore the ads that you see may be selected based on data we process about you, such as your interests, your location, how you use our products, your search queries or the content you view. 

**Information based on cookies:**

The ads that you see may also be selected based on other information learned about you over time through your cookies. This allows third-party advertisers to target based on other information garnered from your browsing history. Cookies using demographic data, location data, search queries, interests and favourites, usage data from our products and sites, as well as the sites and apps of our advertisers and partners. These ads are referred to as "interest-based advertising" in this statement. If you opt out of receiving interest-based advertising, data associated with these cookies will not be used. 

If you wish to opt out of interest based advertising you can do so by following  [this link to the NAI opt-out service](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).  Opting out of interest-based advertising does not mean you will no longer see advertising online. It does mean that the company or companies from which you opt out will no longer show ads that have been tailored to your interests. 

**Data collected by other advertising companies:**

Advertisers sometimes include their own web beacons (or those of their advertising partners) within their advertisements on our platform, enabling them to set and read their own cookie. GoConqr partners with third-party ad companies to deliver advertisements to the platform. These third-parties may place cookies on your device and collect data about your online activities across websites or online services. These companies currently include, but are not limited to:  [AppNexus](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy),  [Google](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) (& [Google partners](https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/9012903) ),  [Rubicon](https://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/),  [Sovrn](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/) and  [PulsePoint](https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy).  You may find more information about each company’s practices, including the choices that it offers, by clicking on the company’s name above. Many of them are also members of the NAI or DAA, which each providing a simple way to opt out of ad targeting from participating companies. 

**Children and advertising:**

Our site is not intended for use by users aged 13 or under, and hence no advertising is targeted at this age group. 

##  HOW TO ACCESS AND CONTROL YOUR DATA 

###  Accessing your data processed by GoConqr 

You can request a file with all personally identifiable information relating to you that has been processed by GoConqr. 

To do this, email contactus@goconqr.com requesting your information. You will receive a response from us within 30 days. You will receive a link to download all the information that has been collected and processed by us. 

###  Controlling general information for providing the GoConqr service 

Details provided when you register with us allow you to manage your account and keep it private – these are integral to the operation of your account. If you do not wish to have these details accessed by us any longer you may delete your account. 

Deleting your account can be done at any stage through your  Account section on the site. Follow the instructions below: 

  * Select “Account” from the drop down menu in the header. 
  * You will be brought the “Personal Details” option. On this page you will see the option to “Cancel Account”. Click on this button. 
  * For security reasons you will be asked to confirm this action using a one-time code sent to you via email. 

Once this is complete, your details and interactions will be deleted from our databases. There will be circumstances whereby we need to maintain some shell information about users. For example, if you have a Premium account and have transacted with us via a third-party payment processor, we are required to keep a record of transactions for legal and reporting requirements. 

###  Controlling communication preferences 

A major element of the GoConqr platform is the ability to connect and learn from others. There are a number features that support knowledge sharing, and communication which are designed to help you to get the most out of GoConqr. We allow you to be notified of activities that may be important to you via alerts and notifications within the platform, via email and via push notifications to any registered mobile device. 

All communication preferences can be controlled by you, so that you only get notified of the elements that are important to you. 

To control what is communicated to you by GoConqr, follow these steps: 

  * Select “Account” from the drop down menu in the header. 
  * For controlling the email updates you receive, select “Email Preferences” on the left hand side menu. 
  * For controlling notifications within the GoConqr application, including mobile push notifications, select “Notifications” on the left hand side menu. 

In these sections you have control over what types of alerts and mail notifications that you receive from us. 

You can also control notifications from Groups that you are a member of within each Group setting. 

###  Advertising 

GoConqr allows advertising from third-parties in order to sustain the free memberships on the platform. 

You can control advertising that is based on identifiable data (i.e. interest based advertising). If you wish to opt out of interest based advertising you can so by following  [ this link ](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) to the NAI opt-out service. Opting out of interest-based advertising does not mean you will no longer see advertising online. It does mean that the company or companies from which you opt out will no longer show ads that have been tailored to your interests. 

##  COOKIES 

Our Service uses "cookies" to distinguish you from other users of our Service and to anonymously track visiting and browsing patterns. 

Cookies are used by most website operators to support website functionaity. A cookie is a small text file implanted on the hard disk of your computer when you visit the site. Cookies can contain information about the user, such as your name, address, e-mail details and your user preferences. 

While cookies and the information they obtain may not identify a living individual on their own, they may be able to do so in combination with other information held by us or a third party. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Service and also allows us to improve our site. 

###  Our use of cookies and similar technologies 

**Sign-in and authentication:** When you sign into your GoConqr account using your account details, we store a unique ID and the time you signed in within an encrypted cookie on your device. This cookie allows you to move from page to page within the site without having to sign in again on each page. 

**Storing your preferences and settings:** Settings that enable our products to operate correctly or that maintain your preferences over time may be stored on your device. For example, for a partially complete quiz we will store your current answers in a cookie so that we can remember your progress if you revisit the quiz at a later time. 

**Social media:** Some of our pages include social media cookies, including those that enable users who are logged in to the social media service to share content via that service. 

**Interest-based advertising:** Some of our third-party advertising partners use cookies to collect data about your online activity and identify your interests so that they can provide advertising that is relevant to you. You can opt out of receiving interest-based advertising as described in the  How to access and control your data section of this privacy statement. 

**Analytics:** In order to provide our products, we use cookies and other identifiers to gather usage and performance data. For example, we use cookies to count the number of unique visitors to a web page or service and to develop other statistics about the operations of our products. This includes cookies from GoConqr and from third-party analytics providers, such as Google Analytics, Alexa and New Relic. 

We prohibit analytics providers from collecting or accessing information that directly identifies you (such as your name or email address). You can opt out of data collection from Google Analytics here: tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout (requires you to install a browser add-on) 

Analytics and performance data collected through cookies is always anonymous and aggregated. 

###  How to control cookies 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but provide controls that allow you to block or delete them. Details on how to block or delete cookies will vary depending on the browser being used, but instructions should be available in each browser's privacy or help documentation. 

Certain features of the GoConqr service depend on cookies. Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use many features of the GoConqr platform and any preferences that are dependent on cookies may be lost. If you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, will be deleted and may need to be recreated. 

##  IMPORTANT PRIVACY INFO 

###  Your rights as the data subject 

GoConqr adheres to applicable data protection laws in the European Economic Area which, if applicable, affords you, the data subject, the following rights: 

  * If the processing of personal data is based on your consent, you have a right to withdraw consent at any time for future processing; 
  * You have a right to request from us, a “data controller” as defined in the law, access to and rectification of your personal data; 
  * You have a right to object to the processing of your personal data; and 

When we process personal data about you, we do so with your consent and/or as necessary to provide the products you use, operate our business, meet our contractual and legal obligations, protect the security of our systems and our customers, or fulfill other legitimate interests of GoConqr as described in the  How we use the data collected section above. 

When we transfer personal data from the European Economic Area, we do so based on a variety of legal mechanisms, as described in “Where we store data” below. 

###  Where we store data 

The data that we collect from you will not be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area which consists of the European Union, Norway and Iceland ("EEA"), unless it is required to be processed by a third party partner. In the instance that information is transferred outside of the EEA, it will only be done so with partners that are fully compliant with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework. Thus ensuring that your data is kept safe. 

Staff maybe engaged in, among other things, processing your subscription, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. A server is a machine that stores and processes data or information. Any communication with our servers will be encrypted using SSL technology. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Service or your account, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access i.e. access to your data by a person who should not have such access. 

###  Security of data 

At GoConqr we are committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. User data is stored on secure cloud infrastructure with access, with access limited to only those employees who require that access to fulfil their function. When we transmit user data over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption. 

###  Retention 

Whilst a user remains a member of GoConqr we will retain the relevant user data needed to operate the member account. 

If a member requests account cancellation then data will cancelled on confirmation of the request. There may be legal or reporting circumstances that require us to keep some high level data regarding a user for an extended time period – e.g payment transaction records for tax purposes. If this is the case, the information will be deleted once the requested time period has passed. 

Upon successful confirmation of your account cancellation request your qualifying data will be deleted from our live database within a matter of minutes. However, a global service such as GoConqr will rely on multiple layers of caches, backups and logs, so fragments of your personal data will remain after your data has been removed from the live database. A summary of the other stores are listed below along with the type of data held and the maximum retention period before this data will be purged. 

**Data store** |  **Typical data held** |  **Retention period***  
---|---|---  
Database backups  |  Full copy of the database, available for disaster recovery  |  Up to 7 days   
Server caches  |  Cached pages, your recent resources, your suggested content.  |  Up to 7 days   
Server logs  |  Requests processed by the platform, including IP address, time, query parameters and error details where errors have occurred.  |  Up to 31 days   
Payment logs  |  Details of when payments were submitted to our payment processing partner, whether the payment was a success and the auth code for the payment  |  Up to 61 days   
Failed jobs  |  Background jobs which have failed, such as emails, push notifications, resource copies, media uploads.  |  Up to 90 days   
  
***** After this period any traces of your data will have been be purged 

###  Disclosure 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Acceptable Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of GoConqr (Examtime Limited), our customers, or others. 

This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

###  Children 

Our services and products are not targeted at children under thirteen (13) years of age. 

If you are under 13 years old you will not be allowed to open an account on our Service or subscribe for any or our services. 

If we discover that we hold or have inadvertently disclosed any personally identifiable data for any user or customer under 13 years of age, it will be deleted from our system to ensure the privacy of the child. 

We also have a number of protections dealing with the personal data of persons under 18 years of age. Specifically, a guardian or parent has the right to review the personal data the Service has collected from their child, have their child’s personal data deleted from the site and also request us to cease obtaining further personal data from the child going forward. 

##  SPECIFIC SERVICES 

###  Mobile Apps 

GoConqr has a range of Mobile Applications (“Apps”) on the iOS and Android platforms (available until July 1st 2019) that allow you to access the platform in a manner optimised for mobile. Our Apps use third party service providers to provide functionality to our users. 

The data gathered by the third party providers relates to the aggregate usage of our service. Our partners include Fabric, Crashlytics, Firebase, Apple and Google Playstore. You may have separate data policies with Apple and Google relating to the download and purchase of mobile apps through their app stores. Compliance with app store policies is assumed when accessing the GoConqr mobile apps. 

These third party service providers are all signed up the EU-US Shield Privacy Frameworks - a mechanism to comply with data protection requirements when transferring personal data from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States in support of transatlantic commerce – ensuring the same level of care with personal data that we extend to you. 

###  GoConqr Campus 

GoConqr Campus provides businesses and educational institutions with a branded portal and Campus groups to facilitate education and knowledge sharing on the GoConqr platform. 

An institution may invite a user to a GoConqr Campus by providing that individual’s email contact details, and institutions that set up a GoConqr Campus undertake that they have permission to share that email for the purpose of setting up a GoConqr Campus. 

You may be invited to join a Campus on GoConqr. As a Campus member, you will receive benefits which include access to Campus groups and announcements. Users that join the GoConqr platform on the basis of a Campus invite are viewed as all other users from a data protection point of view and enjoy the same rights and privileges as all users. 

Your Campus plan may include the ability to access resources without logging in, the ability to create private resources, an ad free GoConqr experience, and the ability to have your performance tracked and certified. Performance can only be tracked by Campus administrators and users with appropriate permissions. Your Campus License Administrator is the data controller for Campus management and reporting. 

If an individual or institution on a SmartShares plan uses a capture form to capture user information on an embedded resource on their own external site, they are the data controller of that information. GoConqr will not access or process any data captured in data capture forms, save for reporting purposes for the SmartShares customer. 

You may leave a Campus at any time while maintaining your membership of GoConqr and access to resources that you have created. 

##  CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY 

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. This page was last updated on 15th May 2018. 

If you have a privacy concern, complaint or a question for the Data Protection team, please email  [contactus@goconqr.com](mailto:contactus@goconqr.com).  We will respond to questions or concerns within 30 days. 

Alternatively you can contact the data protection officer of GoConqr at the following address: GoConqr, Attn: Data Protection Officer, 6a Carrickbrennan Road, Monkstown, Co Dublin, Ireland.
